我们 是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文!
and Steven!
困在一起
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
草
校对
Husky
特效
presisco
压制
玫瑰石英
The Rose Quartz.
你们相信吗
Can you believe it?
她居然亲手将自己奉上
And she just handed herself in.
没错, 你们捉住我了
That's right. You caught me.
星际罪犯玫瑰石
Galactic Criminal Rose Quartz.
我爱粉碎钻石
I love shattering Diamonds.
没事就想着粉碎钻石
I just want to shatter 'em all the time.
你以为粉碎你就能解决问题!
You think shattering's bad?
等着瞧吧, 钻石们可有的是办法让你好受
Wait till the Diamonds get their hands on you.
至少大家都安全了
At least everyone else is safe.
你干什么! 放我走!
What are you doing? Let go of me!
史蒂文!
Steven!
什么…拉尔斯!
What the... Lars!
哦! 看上去我们还是捉到了一只人类
Oh! Looks like we got one of the humans anyway.
只有一个人类, 该怎么办呢
Don't know what we'll do with just one of them,
还是交给钻石们去决定吧
but I guess that's for the Diamonds to decide.
等等, 海蓝宝, 咱们的协议就此终止!
Wait. - Aquamarine, the deal is off.
你只能带走我一个
You were only supposed to take me.
不带任何人类
No humans.
他是人类
That's a human.
哦, 不
Oh, no.
小玫瑰因为她的小算盘没得意而生气了?
Is Rosie upset 'cause her widdle "deal" didn't work?
瞧, 我好悲伤, 我都哭了
Look. I'm so moved, I'm crying.
开玩笑的啦
Just kidding.
这是我的宝石
That's my gem.
托帕石, 你怎么看?
Topaz, what do you think?
我们该不该放她的朋友走呢?
Should we let her friend go?
我同意
I agree.
去吧, 干活吧
Go on. Do your thing.
哦不不不不不不要再这样了
Oh, no, no, no, no. Not again.
我会向钻石们报告这位新囚犯的
I'll go let the Diamonds know about our little prisoner.
来说说, 玫瑰, 我看上去怎么样?
Say, Rose, how do I look?
糟糕, 矮小, 还刻薄!
Awful, small, and mean!
这就是你如何骗取那么多石的信任
Is that how you flattered so many Gems
加入你的叛军联盟的吗?
into joining your rebellion?
可爱死了
How cute.
托帕石, 我认为你还能自如操作飞船
Topaz, I trust you'll still be able to fly the ship
尽管你…哎你懂的…身上多了点东西?
despite your... you know....additions?
史蒂文, 这都是你的错
Steven, this is all your fault.
这些奇怪的外星人之类的 都是因为你, 对不对?
All this weird alien stuff -- this is 'cause of you, isn't it?
是的, 当然了!
Yes, of course it is!
这也是为什么我用我自己 交换你们的安全!
That's why I turned myself in -- to save all of you!
哈, 可它进行的没那么顺利是不是?
Well, it didn't really work out too well, did it?
除你以外所有人都安全下船了
Well, everyone else managed to get off the ship.
所以, 你当时在哪?
So, where were you?
我狂跑, 然后藏起来了, 史蒂文
I ran and hid, Steven,
就像任何有理智的人会…做
like any sensible person would...do
如果他想被困在一艘飞船上
if they wanted to get trapped on a ship.
哦
Oh.
拉尔斯
Lars.
莎蒂陷入了危险, 可我什么都没做
Sadie was in trouble, and I didn't do anything.
事实上, 等等, 我还是有所作为的
Actually, wait. I did do something.
我逃命, 我躲了起来, 就像我一直以来做的
I ran and hid just like I always do.
就像我没有去参加聚餐
Just like I ran from the potluck.
可你被绑架了
But you were abducted.
这不是你的错
That's not your fault.
不, 我把蛋糕卷扔了 然后跑掉了
No, I trashed my roll and ran away.
然后我才被绑架的
Then I was abducted.
哦, 为什么我就不能好好和人分享食物?!
Oh, why couldn't I just let people eat my food?!
我们得尽快把你送出去
We have to get you out of here.
就交给我吧
Here, just leave it to me.
嘿! 瞧! 你捉到玫瑰石英了!
Hey! Look! You have Rose Quartz!
为什么还要留着他? 他一点用都没有!
Why bother with him? He's worthless!
真是谢谢啊, 史蒂文
Thanks a lot, Steven.
不! 我是指…没太大用, 不是没一点用
No! I meant like "worth less", not "worthless"
跟…跟我比的话
like...relative to me.
我至少还是一个不错的坐垫
At least I make a great seat cushion.
舒服不, 你个大香蕉?
You feeling cozy, you big banana?
我不认为她能听见
I don't think she's listening.
你能听见我吗, 你这个--杰米怎么说的来着?
Can you hear me, you -- What was it Jamie said?
你这危险的大黄衣?
You dangerous yellow coat?
她当然听不见你, 史蒂文
Of course - she can't hear you, Steven.
她戴着那对大耳麦呢
She's got those big headphones on.
起飞时那些水晶战士一定是
Those Crystal Gems must have screwed up the engine
把发动机弄坏了
during takeoff.
托帕石, 去把它修好
Topaz, go fix it.
拉尔斯, 找找能帮助咱们的东西
Lars, look for something that can help us.
一个分解器
A destabilizer.
太完美了!
That's perfect!
一个分什么?
A destaba-what?
它是一种可以破坏宝石人物理形态的武器
It's a weapon that disrupts a Gem's physical form.
酷, 多谢解释
Cool. Thanks for explaining.
但我还不懂它啥意思
I still don't know what that means.
听我讲, 我有一个计划
Just hear me out. I have a plan.
我需要你的帮助
I'm gonna need you to be my arms.
呃, 好吧
Ugh. Fine.
拉尔斯, 把我的裤子脱下来
Lars, pull my pants off.
什么?!
What?!
相信我! 我想帮你
Trust me! I'm trying to save you.
可如果我不想被救呢?
What if I don't want to be saved?
如果我只想被困在这里在宇宙里漂泊呢
What if I want to stay trapped here and fly around space,
而且为什么要脱你裤子, 你个怪胎?!
and why your pants, you weirdo?!
脱就是了!
Just do it!
呃, 好 脱过了
Ugh. There. I did it.
很好, 现在把其中一只裤腿系成一个套索
Great. Now tie one of the legs into a lasso.
我做不到, 裤子在地上
I can't. They're on the floor.
它们为什么会在地上?!
What are they doing on the floor?!
我不知道, 史蒂文, 我们为什么会在宇宙里?
I don't know, Steven. What are we doing in space?
拉尔斯, 捡起来, 然后把它们系成一个套索
Lars, pick them up - and then tie them into a lasso.
呃, 随你吧
Ugh. Fine.
喔, 成功啦
Wow. It worked.
我们到家喽
We're back home.
好计划
Great plan.
现在套住分解器
Now lasso the destabilizer.
我还是不知道那是什么东西
I still don't know what that is.
那个, 那个棍子
That. That thing.
加把劲啊, 拉尔斯, 你能做到的
Come on, Lars. You can do it.
呃, 成
Ugh. Fine.
加油, 再试一次
Come on. Just one more try.
我不想再试一次了
I don't want to try again.
拉尔斯, 扔出套索!
Lars, throw the lasso!
知道了!
Fine!
你到底怎么了, 拉尔斯?!
What is your problem, Lars?!
为什么要这么做?!
Why did you do that?!
为什么你觉得我能干成一件事?!
Why do you think I'm capable of anything?!
你觉得我能, 我能做到, 但我做不到!
You think I can do - all this stuff, but I can't!
我做不到, 因为…
I can't because...
我是一个软蛋, 史蒂文
I'm a wuss, Steven.
我很害怕
I'm just afraid.
我一直都这么活在恐惧和无知当中
I've always just been stupid and afraid.
不像你, 总是在帮助他人
Not like you. You're always helping people.
你从不畏惧什么
You're never afraid.
拉尔斯…
Lars...
我现在就感到很害怕
I'm afraid right now.
我以为只要我交出我自己, 一切就会重归原样, 但是…
I thought if I turned myself in, it'd fix everything, but...
我不想这么做, 拉尔斯
I don't want to do this, Lars.
我以前去过宇宙, 可不是像这样去的
I've been to space before, but not like this.
她们要将我直接交给那些残暴的首领手中
They're taking me straight to their terrible leaders
她们想毁掉地球, 也想毁掉我
that want to destroy Earth and destroy me
只是为了一些我从未做过的事
for something I never even did.
我想要救所有人, 可我连那都做不到
I just wanted to save everyone, but I couldn't even do that
因为, 你瞧, 你还在这里
because, look -- you're still here.
史蒂文
Steven.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不知道该如何将你救出去
I don't know how I'm gonna get you out of this.
我们会想办法的
We'll figure it out.
我们距离到达目的地大概还有
We've got like a billion light-years
几十亿光年的 不是吗?
till we get there, right?
有史以来第一次,
For the first time ever,
你要向积极的一面看了?
you're gonna look on the bright side?
你 你不需要骗自己的
Y-You don't have to sugarcoat this,
得了吧 你从来没这样积极过的
but come on, you never do that.
你一直都毫无保留地和我抱怨一切都是那么糟糕
You're always real with me about how much everything sucks.
好吧, 你是对的
Okay. You're right.
这真的真的糟透了, 史蒂文
This is really, really messed up, Steven.
但你知道还有什么更糟的吗?
You know what's even more messed up?
尽管这让你陷入了大危机
Even though you're in huge trouble
而且全部都是我的错…
and it's all my fault...
我却很高兴有你陪着我
I'm kind of glad you're here.
我…
I...
我不希望独自一个人面对这一切
I don't want to be alone right now.
我是不是糟透了?
Isn't that awful?
伙计, 到现在这一步
Dude, at this point,
一切都糟透了
everything is awful.
我很乐意抱抱你, 但我的胳膊被困住了
I'd give you a hug, but I can't use my arms.
我可以试试用我的腿抱你, 但估计会挺恶心的
I could try using my legs, but it might be weird.
这, 这太美好了
That's so, so beautiful.
尽管一切都将终结
Even in the clutches of certain doom,
你们还是很高兴拥有彼此
you're happy to have each other.
托 托帕石
T-T-Topaz.
我不知道托帕石该怎么做, 如果她没有托帕石的话
I don't know what Topaz would do if she didn't have Topaz.
我一直都想要告诉我
I've always wanted to tell me
我对我有多大帮助
how I'm helping me through this,
但我与我之间永远都有人阻挡着!
but there's always someone between us!
她们总是将我们送往这些不幸的任务
They're always sending me on these miserable missions.
我总是骗自己我喜欢这些任务
I'm always pretending I'm fine with it.
我必须要假装我很好
I have to pretend I'm fine.
但你们, 你们对彼此如此坦诚
But you two --you're so honest and open...
那么
so
我想帮助你们
I want to help you guys.
你们需要什么?
What do you need?
下船的方法
A way off this ship.
还有我的裤子
And my pants.
好, 你们可以用逃生舱
All right. - You can use this escape pod.
我会为你们设下地球的坐标
I'll set the coordinates for Earth.
好了, 拉尔斯, 快跳进去这件事就完成了
All right, Lars, just get in and let it do its thing.
呃, 你在说什么呢! 你也会跟我一起走, 不是吗?
Guh. What are you talking about? You're coming, right?
我不能, 我已经交出我自己了
I can't. I turned myself in.
我还是要走的
I still got to go.
总有人需要为我母亲做的事付出代价
Someone's got to pay for what my mom did.
但你不是不想这么做吗?
But you don't want to do this?
伙计, 别管那么多了, 快走吧
Dude, forget it. Let's just go.
我...
I-
托帕石, 你还在下面磨蹭什么呢
Topaz, what are you still doing down here,
你这大石块?
you big boulder?
我们已经快到母星了
We're almost to Homeworld.
你…在…做…什么?
What...are...you...doing?
等等, 我能解释
Look, I can explain.
呃, 他们置心长谈
Um, they had this whole heartfelt thing
有彼此多么好, 你错过了
about being there for each other, and you missed it.
实在是太感人了
It was so moving.
不! 等等!
No! Wait!
我什么都看不到, 咱们的逃跑计划呢?
I can't see what's happening. Are we still escaping?
不存在的! 没人逃跑!
No! Nobody's escaping!
海蓝宝, 咱们好好沟通一下
Aquamarine, let's talk about this.
对, 我我想你也不是真的想伤害我们
Yeah, I-I bet you don't really want to hurt us.
你--你只是表现得很刻薄
You -- You probably just act mean
因为内心深处恐惧自己的弱小
because deep down you're afraid you're weak.
来吧, 尽情讲, 我们都在分享情感呢
Go ahead. Let it out. We're all sharing right now.
托帕石, 你只有一项工作
Topaz, you had one job,
如果你不想做这份工作
and if you're not gonna do it,
那你已经毫无用处了!
you're of no use to me!
喔哦!
Ooh!
叛乱…是吧?
So...a revolt, huh?
在此之后你又打算怎么做?
And what do you plan to do after this?
回到钻石身边? 拿着我的宝石?
Go back to the Diamonds? My gem in your hand?
她们肯定要高兴坏了
I'm sure they'll love that.
而你们也会被重赏
You'll be rewarded handsomely
被分离, 被粉碎
by being separated and shattered.
我在想什么呢!
What was I thinking?
这就是你们这群融合体的毛病
That's the problem with you fusions.
迟早, 你们都变得感情用事
Sooner or later, - you all become sentimental.
我们到了
We're here.
这样, 只要你们解除融合
Look, just unfuse,
我们就不再提起这件事了
and we'll never speak of this again.
托帕石, 你不必这么做
Topaz, you don't have to do this.
等等, 拉尔斯!
Wait. Lars!
史蒂文, 她们要把我们送到哪里?!
Steven, where are they taking us?!
我不知道!
I don't know!
史蒂文!
Steven!
拉尔斯!
Lars!